kickboardforteachers.com 2019-10-31

# Website Privacy Policy | Kickboard

Welcome to Kickboard, Inc.’s company website. Like many hosted service providers, the name of our company is also the name of our suite of product and service solutions. In this policy we refer to our instructional management software platform and service suite as “Kickboard” and to the Kickboard, Inc. entity as “Company” or “we.”

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit [http://www.kickboardforschools.com](http://www.kickboardforschools.com/) (the “Company Site”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information. The Company Site is intended for a general audience. Although we may permit educators and parents to access the Kickboard instructional management software platform through links provided on the Company Site, access to and use of Kickboard is governed by separate agreements with customers and authorized Kickboard users, including our Kickboard Platform Privacy Policy and our Platform Acceptable Use Policy. In addition, this policy does not apply to information collected by us offline or through any other means or by any third party, including through application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Company Site.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use the Company Site. By accessing or using the Company Site, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of the Company Site after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

### Children Under the Age of 13 and Student Education Records

The Company Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age or for use in connection with student education records. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13, or information that may comprise student education records, through the Company Site. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on the Company Site or on or through any of its features. In addition, regardless of age, you should never provide student education records on or through the Company Site. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent or any education records of a minor student through the Company Site we will delete that information.

To learn more about our practices with respect to student information entered into the Kickboard platform and how and when FERPA may apply, please refer to our Platform Privacy Policy.

### Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

#### We collect several types of information from and about users of the Company Site, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, employer, job title, postal address, email address and telephone number (“ **personal information** ”);
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access the Company Site and usage details.

#### We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the Company Site, such usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies.
  * From third parties, for example, display advertising providers and social networks.

#### **Information You Provide to Us.** The information we collect on or through the Company Site may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on the Company Site, such as requests for marketing or other information.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.

#### **Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies.** As you navigate through and interact with the Company Site, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to the Company Site, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Company Site.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (referred to as behavioral tracking). [Click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed) for information on how you can opt out of behavioral tracking on the Company Site and how we respond to web browser signals and other mechanisms that enable consumers to exercise choice about behavioral tracking.

The information we collect automatically may include personal information, or we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve the Company Site and to deliver more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize the Company Site according to your individual interests.
  * Recognize you when you return to the Company Site.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the Company Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to the Company Site.
  * **Flash Cookies.** Certain features of the Company Site may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on the Company Site. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website.
  * **Web Beacons.** Pages of our the Company Site and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

### Third-party Use of Tracking Technologies.

Some content or applications on the Company Site are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. These third parties may use cookies, alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies, to collect information about you when you use the Company Site. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

### How We Use Your Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present the Company Site and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to the Company Site or any of our products or services.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties’ goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please check the relevant box located on the email subscription account profile).

### Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our guests to the Company Site, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. In addition, we may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company’s assets.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our Terms of Use.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our customers or others.

### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of the Company Site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to support@kickboardforteachers.com.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you through a notice on the Company Site home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for periodically visiting the Company Site and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

### Contact Information

If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact our Support Team at: Kickboard, Inc., 1824 Oretha Castle Haley Blvd., New Orleans, LA 70113 or via email at: [support@kickboardforschools.com](mailto:support@kickboardforschools.com "support@kickboardforteachers.com"). In the U.S. you may also call us toll-free at: 1 (855) 456-1946.

_Last modified June 16, 2014_
